Narrator: 1
F: Success is 99 per cent failure.
Narrator: 2
M: You have to go through some adversity to be successful.
Narrator: 3
F: Use what you’ve been through as fuel, believe in yourself and be unstoppable.
Narrator: 4
M: A hero is an ordinary individual who finds the strength to persevere
and endure in spite of overwhelming obstacles.
Narrator: 5
F: He who believes is strong; he who doubts is weak. Strong convictions precede great actions.
Narrator: 6
M: Sometimes you don’t realize your own strength
until you come face to face with your greatest weakness.
Narrator: 7
F: Some people will just go with the flow of things in life,
while others will fight against the currents and go upstream to reach their destiny.